A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Campaigns, Series 5 FA440
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Campaigns, 1956-1970; 5; 98.04 Cubic Feet 216 containers including but not limited to: 45 letter document boxes, 167 legal document boxes.
  - 1960 U.S. Presidential Campaign, 6
    - Petitions to Republican National Convention to Draft Rockefeller for President, 1960 (Box 78, Folder 1030)
      California.
    - Petitions to Republican National Convention to Draft Rockefeller for President, 1960 (Box 78, Folder 1031)
    - Petitions to Republican National Convention to Draft Rockefeller for President, 1960 (Box 78, Folder 1032)
    - Petitions to Republican National Convention to Draft Rockefeller for President, 1960 (Box 78, Folder 1033)
    - Petitions to Republican National Convention to Draft Rockefeller for President, 1960 (Box 78, Folder 1034)
    - Petitions to Republican National Convention to Draft Rockefeller for President, 1960 (Box 78, Folder 1035)
      Colorado.
    - Petitions to Republican National Convention to Draft Rockefeller for President, 1960 (Box 79, Folder 1036)
    - Petitions to Republican National Convention to Draft Rockefeller for President, 1960 (Box 79, Folder 1037)
    - Petitions to Republican National Convention to Draft Rockefeller for President, 1960 (Box 79, Folder 1038)
    - Petitions to Republican National Convention to Draft Rockefeller for President, 1960 (Box 79, Folder 1039)
    - Petitions to Republican National Convention to Draft Rockefeller for President, 1960 (Box 79, Folder 1040)
    - Petitions to Republican National Convention to Draft Rockefeller for President, 1960 (Box 79, Folder 1041)
    - Petitions to Republican National Convention to Draft Rockefeller for President, 1960 (Box 79, Folder 1042)
    - Petitions to Republican National Convention to Draft Rockefeller for President, 1960 (Box 80, Folder 1043)
    - Petitions to Republican National Convention to Draft Rockefeller for President, 1960 (Box 80, Folder 1044)
      Connecticut.
    - Petitions to Republican National Convention to Draft Rockefeller for President, 1960 (Box 80, Folder 1045)
      Delaware.
    - Petitions to Republican National Convention to Draft Rockefeller for President, 1960 (Box 80, Folder 1046)
      District of Columbia.
    - Petitions to Republican National Convention to Draft Rockefeller for President, 1960 (Box 80, Folder 1047)
      Florida.
    - Petitions to Republican National Convention to Draft Rockefeller for President, 1960 (Box 80, Folder 1048)
      Indiana, Iowa, Kansas, Maine.
    - Petitions to Republican National Convention to Draft Rockefeller for President, 1960 (Box 80, Folder 1049)
      Illinois.
    - Petitions to Republican National Convention to Draft Rockefeller for President, 1960 (Box 80, Folder 1050)
    - Petitions to Republican National Convention to Draft Rockefeller for President, 1960 (Box 80, Folder 1051)
      Maryland.
    - Petitions to Republican National Convention to Draft Rockefeller for President, 1960 (Box 80, Folder 1052)
      Massachusetts.
    - Petitions to Republican National Convention to Draft Rockefeller for President, 1946 (Box 80, Folder 1053)
      Michigan, Minnesota.
    - Petitions to Republican National Convention to Draft Rockefeller for President, 1960 (Box 80, Folder 1054)
      Missouri, Montana, Nevada.
    - Petitions to Republican National Convention to Draft Rockefeller for President, 1960 (Box 80, Folder 1055)
      New Hampshire, New Jersey, New Mexico.
    - Petitions to Republican National Convention to Draft Rockefeller for President, 1960 (Box 80, Folder 1056)
      New York.
    - Petitions to Republican National Convention to Draft Rockefeller for President, 1960 (Box 81, Folder 1057)
    - Petitions to Republican National Convention to Draft Rockefeller for President, 1960 (Box 81, Folder 1058)
    - Petitions to Republican National Convention to Draft Rockefeller for President, 1960 (Box 81, Folder 1059)
    - Petitions to Republican National Convention to Draft Rockefeller for President, 1960 (Box 81, Folder 1060)
    - Petitions to Republican National Convention to Draft Rockefeller for President, 1960 (Box 81, Folder 1061)
    - Petitions to Republican National Convention to Draft Rockefeller for President, 1960 (Box 81, Folder 1062)
      North Carolina, North Dakota.
    - Petitions to Republican National Convention to Draft Rockefeller for President, 1960 (Box 81, Folder 1063)
      Ohio.
    - Petitions to Republican National Convention to Draft Rockefeller for President, 1960 (Box 82, Folder 1064)
      Oregon.
    - Petitions to Republican National Convention to Draft Rockefeller for President, 1960 (Box 82, Folder 1065)
      Pennsylvania.
    - Petitions to Republican National Convention to Draft Rockefeller for President, 1960 (Box 82, Folder 1066)
    - Petitions to Republican National Convention to Draft Rockefeller for President, 1960 (Box 82, Folder 1067)
    - Petitions to Republican National Convention to Draft Rockefeller for President, 1960 (Box 82, Folder 1068)
    - Petitions to Republican National Convention to Draft Rockefeller for President, 1960 (Box 82, Folder 1069)
      Rhode Island, South Dakota, Tennessee, Utah, Vermont and Virginia.
    - Petitions to Republican National Convention to Draft Rockefeller for President, 1960 (Box 82, Folder 1070)
      Washington, Wyoming, Wisconsin.
    - Thank-You Letters to Office Workers, 1960 (Box 82, Folder 1071)
    - Letters Received with Coupons, 1960 (Box 82, Folder 1072)
    - Letters Offering Help with Campaign, 1960 (Box 82, Folder 1073)
    - Rockefeller Clubs - California, 1960 (Box 83, Folder 1074)
    - Campaign Literature, 1960 (Box 83, Folder 1075)
    - Correspondence to Draft Rockefeller, 1960 (Box 83, Folder 1076)
    - New York State Independent Citizens for Nixon - Lodge, Check Register, 1960 October 10-November 5 (Box 83, Folder 1077)
    - New York State Independent Citizens for Nixon - Lodge, Check Register, 1960 'October 4-November 8 (Box 83, Folder 1078)
    - New York State Independent Citizens for Nixon - Lodge, Check Register, 1960 'October 19-November 5 (Box 83, Folder 1079)
    - New Yorkers for Nixon - Check Register, 1960 September 6-October 6 (Box 83, Folder 1080)
    - New Yorkers for Nixon - Check Register, 1959-1960 (Box 83, Folder 1081)
      Balance in account to Citizens for Nixon-Lodge.
    - Nixon Speakers Manual for Nixon Sports Advisory Committee, 1960 (Box 84, Folder 1082)
    - Volunteers for Nixon Chairman's Manual, 1960 (Box 84, Folder 1083)
    - Draft Rockefeller - Correspondence in Support, 1960 (Box 84, Folder 1084)
    - Draft Rockefeller - Correspondence in Support, 1960 (Box 84, Folder 1085)
    - Draft Rockefeller - State Chairmen, 1960 (Box 84, Folder 1086)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1960 (Box 84, Folder 1087)
    - Letters to Prospective Speakers, 1960 (Box 84, Folder 1088)
    - Speakers Committee Correspondence, 1960 (Box 84, Folder 1089)
    - Speakers Committee for Nixon - Lodge, Leon J. Weil File, 1960 (Box 84, Folder 1090)
    - Nixon - Lodge Correspondence, 1960 (Box 84, Folder 1091)
  - 1964 U.S. Presidential Campaign, 7
    - Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 85, Folder 1092)
    - Advance Magazine Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 85, Folder 1093)
    - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1962-1964 (Box 85, Folder 1094)
    - Isaac Koenigsberg Activities, 1961 (Box 85, Folder 1095)
    - Budget Control, Rockefeller-Javits, 1962 (Box 85, Folder 1096)
    - News Clipping Service, Example, 1964 May (Box 85, Folder 1097)
    - Request for Information Volunteer Forms, 1963 (Box 85, Folder 1098)
    - Regional Directors, 1964 (Box 85, Folder 1099)
    - Personnel Matters, 1964 (Box 85, Folder 1100)
    - Gubernatorial Press Releases, 1964 March-April (Box 85, Folder 1101)
    - Rockefeller for President Press Releases, 1964 February-March (Box 85, Folder 1102)
    - Gubernatorial Press Releases on State Legislation, 1964 March-April (Box 85, Folder 1103)
    - National Campaign Committee Headquarters Phone List, 1964 (Box 85, Folder 1104)
    - Executive Offices, 1964 (Box 85, Folder 1105)
    - Alexander Halpern Correspondence, 1964 (Box 85, Folder 1106)
    - Campaign Photographs and Press Kit (empty), 1964 (Box 85, Folder 1107)
  - 1968 U.S. Presidential Campaign, 8
    - Weekly Budget Reports, 1968 (Box 86, Folder 1108-1109)
    - Message to New York State Legistlature, 1968 (Box 86, Folder 1110)
    - Town Meetings, Schedules, 1968 (Box 86, Folder 1111)
    - NAR Schedules (Box 86, Folder 1112)
    - Bills - Jerry Danzig, 1965-1968 (Box 86, Folder 1113)
    - Transportation Bond Issue, 1967 (Box 86, Folder 1114)
    - Advertising, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1115)
    - Women Delegates (by State), 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1116)
    - Republican State Central Committee - List of Officers, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1117)
    - National Committeewomen, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1118)
    - Republican National Committee, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1119)
    - NAR State Committees, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1120)
    - Arizona, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1121)
    - California, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1122)
    - Colorado, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1123)
    - Connecticut, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1124)
    - Delaware, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1125)
    - District of Columbia, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1126)
    - Florida, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1127)
    - Georgia, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1128)
    - Hawaii and Idaho, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1129)
    - Illinois, Indiana, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1130)
    - Kansas, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1131)
    - Kentucky, Lousiana, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1132)
    - Maine, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1133)
    - Maryland, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1134)
    - Massachusetts, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1135)
    - Michigan, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1136)
    - Minnesota, Missouri, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1137)
    - Nebraska, Nevada, New Hampshire, New Jersey, New Mexico, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1138)
    - New York, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1139)
    - North Carolina, Ohio, Oregon, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1140)
    - Pennsylvania, Puerto Rico, Rhode Island, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 1141)
    - Tennessee, Texas, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1142)
    - Utah, Virginia, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1143)
    - Washington, Wisconsin, Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1144)
    - Finance Committee, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1145)
    - Hawkes Letter Control Book, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1146)
    - Petition Control Book, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1147)
    - Petitions to Nominate NAR, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1148)
    - Budget - Boles, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1149)
    - Campaign Materials (Boles), 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1150)
    - Correspondence - Incoming - Boles, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1151)
    - Correspondence - Outgoing - Boles, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1152)
    - Citizens Mailings, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1153)
    - Citizens Manual, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1154)
    - Daily Reports to Boles, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1155)
    - Delegate Mailings, 1968 (Box 88, Folder 1156)
    - National Bipartisan Movement, Inc., 1968 (Box 89, Folder 1157-1158)
    - Staff Memoranda - Special Groups, 1968 (Box 89, Folder 1159)
    - Personnel - Special Groups, 1968 (Box 89, Folder 1160)
    - "We Want Rockefeller Committee - Curtis Perkins, 1968 (Box 89, Folder 1161)
    - Citizens Activities - Organization and Suggestions, 1968 (Box 89, Folder 1162)
    - Petitions: Presidential Reference Poll, 1968 (Box 89, Folder 1163)
    - National Citizens Committee Organization Chart, 1968 (Box 89, Folder 1164)
    - Rubeck and Company (Bumper Stickers), 1968 (Box 89, Folder 1165)
    - Rockefeller for President - News Releases, 1968 June 6-July 12 (Box 89, Folder 1166)
    - Rockefeller for President - News Releases, 1968 July 8-28 (Box 89, Folder 1167)
    - NAR's Schedules, 1968 June 11-July 31 (Box 89, Folder 1168)
    - Rockefeller for President - Staff Lists, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 1169)
    - Rockefeller for President - Staff Meetings, Strategy memos, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 1170)
    - Rockefeller for President - State Lists, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 1171)
    - Rockefeller for President - Status Reports, Store Fronts, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 1172)
    - Rockefeller for President - Bumper Sticker Allocations, Calendars, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 1173)
    - Rockefeller for President - Census Extract, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 1174)
    - Rockefeller for President - Expenses, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 1175)
    - Rockefeller for President - Impact and Follow up for; A Guide to Coordinators, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 1176)
    - Rockefeller for President - Bumper Stickers Inventory, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 1177)
    - Rockefeller for President - Materials Distribution, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 1178)
    - Rockefeller for President - Memos re: Distribution, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 1179)
    - Rockefeller for President - Mobile Vans, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 1180)
    - Rockefeller for President - Night Letters, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 1181)
    - Rockefeller for President - Mailing List, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 1182)
    - Rockefeller for President - Petitions, Program Allocation, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 1183)
    - Rockefeller for President - Posters, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 1184)
    - Rockefeller for President - Reports, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 1185)
    - Rockefeller for President - Rockefeller Biography, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 1186)
    - Rockefeller for President - Sayeru, Jamie, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 1187)
    - Rockefeller for President - Shipping, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 1188)
    - Rockefeller for President - Smith, Ed - Reports to Boles, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 1189)
    - Rockefeller for President - State Committees and Chairman, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 1190)
    - Rockefeller for President - State Inventories, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 1191)
    - Rockefeller for President - Top Priority States and Contacts, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 1192)
    - Rockefeller for President - Top Priority States - Colorado, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 1193)
    - Rockefeller for President - Top Priority States - Connecticut, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 1194)
    - Rockefeller for President - Top Priority States - Florida, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 1195)
    - Rockefeller for President - Top Priority States - Hawaii, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 1196)
    - Rockefeller for President - Top Priority States - Idaho, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 1197)
    - Rockefeller for President - Top Priority States - Illinois, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 1198)
    - Rockefeller for President - Top Priority States - Indiana, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 1199)
    - Rockefeller for President - Top Priority States - Iowa, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1200)
    - Rockefeller for President - Top Priority States - Kansas, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1201)
    - Rockefeller for President - Top Priority States - Kentucky, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1202)
    - Rockefeller for President - Top Priority States - Maine, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1203)
    - Rockefeller for President - Top Priority States - Maryland, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1204)
    - Rockefeller for President - Top Priority States - Massachusetts, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1205)
    - Rockefeller for President - Top Priority States - Michigan, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1206)
    - Rockefeller for President - Top Priority States - Minnesota, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1207)
    - Rockefeller for President - Top Priority States - Missouri, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1208)
    - Rockefeller for President - Top Priority States - Nevada, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1209)
    - Rockefeller for President - Top Priority States - New Jersey, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1210)
    - Rockefeller for President - Top Priority States - New Mexico, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1211)
    - Rockefeller for President - Top Priority States - North Dakota, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1212)
    - Rockefeller for President - Top Priority States - Ohio, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1213)
    - Rockefeller for President - Top Priority States - Oklahoma, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1214)
    - Rockefeller for President - Top Priority States - Pennsylvania, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1215)
    - Rockefeller for President - Top Priority States - Texas, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1216)
    - Rockefeller for President - Top Priority States - Utah, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1217)
    - Rockefeller for President - Top Priority States - Vermont, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1218)
    - Rockefeller for President - Top Priority States - Virginia, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1219)
    - Rockefeller for President - Top Priority States - Washington, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1220)
    - Rockefeller for President - Top Priority States - Wisconsin, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1221)
    - Rockefeller for President - Top Priority States - Wyoming, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1222)
    - Rockefeller for President - Cities - Advance Reports - Akron, OH, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1223)
    - Rockefeller for President - Cities - Advance Reports - Baltimore, MD, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1224)
    - Rockefeller for President - Cities - Advance Reports - Boston, MA, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1225)
    - Rockefeller for President - Cities - Advance Reports - Chicago, IL, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1226)
    - Rockefeller for President - Cities - Advance Reports - Cincinnati, OH, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1227)
    - Rockefeller for President - Cities - Advance Reports - Cleveland, OH, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1228)
    - Rockefeller for President - Cities - Advance Reports - Columbus, OH, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1229)
    - Rockefeller for President - Cities - Advance Reports - Dallas, TX, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1230)
    - Rockefeller for President - Cities - Advance Reports - Dayton, OH, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1231)
    - Rockefeller for President - Cities - Advance Reports - Detroit, MI, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1232)
    - Rockefeller for President - Cities - Advance Reports - Grand Rapids, MI, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1233)
    - Rockefeller for President - Cities - Advance Reports - Kansas City, MO, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1234)
    - Rockefeller for President - Cities - Advance Reports - Lansing, MI, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1235)
    - Rockefeller for President - Cities - Advance Reports - Newark, NJ, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1236)
    - Rockefeller for President - Cities - Advance Reports - Peoria, IL, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1237)
    - Rockefeller for President - Cities - Advance Reports - St. Louis, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 1238)
    - George Hinman - Labor - News Clippings, 1968 (Box 92, Folder 1239)
    - George Hinman - Young Republicans, 1968 (Box 92, Folder 1240)
    - George Hinman - The South, 1968 (Box 92, Folder 1241)
    - George Hinman - Republican Convention, 1968 (Box 92, Folder 1242)
    - George Hinman - "Negro", 1968 (Box 92, Folder 1243)
    - George Hinman - Convention Delegate Analysis, 1968 (Box 92, Folder 1244)
    - George Hinman - Republican National Convention - Portland, OR meeting, 1968 (Box 92, Folder 1245)
    - George Hinman - Republican National Convention - Balloting, 1968 (Box 92, Folder 1246)
    - George Hinman - 1964 Delegates, 1968 (Box 92, Folder 1247)
    - George Hinman - State Files - RNC Delegate Information - Alabama, 1968 (Box 92, Folder 1248)
    - George Hinman - State Files - RNC Delegate Information - Alaska, 1968 (Box 92, Folder 1249)
    - George Hinman - State Files - RNC Delegate Information - Arizona, 1968 (Box 92, Folder 1250)
    - George Hinman - State Files - RNC Delegate Information - Arkansas, 1968 (Box 92, Folder 1251)
    - George Hinman - State Files - RNC Delegate Information - California, 1968 (Box 92, Folder 1252)
    - George Hinman - State Files - RNC Delegate Information - Colorado, 1968 (Box 92, Folder 1253)
    - George Hinman - State Files - RNC Delegate Information - Connecticut, 1968 (Box 92, Folder 1254)
    - George Hinman - State Files - RNC Delegate Information - Delaware, 1968 (Box 92, Folder 1255)
    - George Hinman - State Files - RNC Delegate Information - District of Columbia, 1968 (Box 92, Folder 1256)
    - George Hinman - State Files - RNC Delegate Information - Florida, 1968 (Box 92, Folder 1257)
    - George Hinman - State Files - RNC Delegate Information - Georgia, 1968 (Box 92, Folder 1258)
    - George Hinman - State Files - RNC Delegate Information - Hawaii, 1968 (Box 92, Folder 1259)
    - George Hinman - State Files - RNC Delegate Information - Idaho, 1968 (Box 92, Folder 1260)
    - George Hinman - State Files - RNC Delegate Information - Illinois, 1968 (Box 92, Folder 1261)
    - George Hinman - State Files - RNC Delegate Information - Indiana, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 1262)
    - George Hinman - State Files - RNC Delegate Information - Kentucky, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 1263)
    - George Hinman - State Files - RNC Delegate Information - Louisiana, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 1264)
    - George Hinman - State Files - RNC Delegate Information - Maine, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 1265)
    - George Hinman - State Files - RNC Delegate Information - Maryland, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 1266)
    - George Hinman - State Files - RNC Delegate Information - Massachusetts, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 1267)
    - George Hinman - State Files - RNC Delegate Information - Michigan, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 1268)
    - George Hinman - State Files - RNC Delegate Information - Minnesota, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 1269)
    - George Hinman - State Files - RNC Delegate Information - Mississippi, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 1270)
    - George Hinman - State Files - RNC Delegate Information - Missouri, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 1271)
    - George Hinman - State Files - RNC Delegate Information - Montana, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 1272)
    - George Hinman - State Files - RNC Delegate Information - Nebraska, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 1273)
    - George Hinman - State Files - RNC Delegate Information - Nevada, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 1274)
    - George Hinman - State Files - RNC Delegate Information - New Hampshire, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 1275)
    - George Hinman - State Files - RNC Delegate Information - New Jersey, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 1276)
    - George Hinman - State Files - RNC Delegate Information - New Mexico, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 1277)
    - George Hinman - State Files - RNC Delegate Information - New York, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 1278)
    - George Hinman - State Files - RNC Delegate Information - North Carolina, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 1279)
    - George Hinman - State Files - RNC Delegate Information - North Dakota, 1968 (Box 94, Folder 1280)
    - George Hinman - State Files - RNC Delegate Information - Ohio, 1968 (Box 94, Folder 1281)
    - George Hinman - State Files - RNC Delegate Information - Oklahoma, 1968 (Box 94, Folder 1282)
    - George Hinman - State Files - RNC Delegate Information - Oregon, 1968 (Box 94, Folder 1283)
    - George Hinman - State Files - RNC Delegate Information - Pennsylvania, 1968 (Box 94, Folder 1284)
    - George Hinman - State Files - RNC Delegate Information - Puerto Rico, 1968 (Box 94, Folder 1285)
    - George Hinman - State Files - RNC Delegate Information - Rhode Island, 1968 (Box 94, Folder 1286)
    - George Hinman - State Files - RNC Delegate Information - South Carolina, 1968 (Box 94, Folder 1287)
    - George Hinman - State Files - RNC Delegate Information - South Dakota, 1968 (Box 94, Folder 1288)
    - George Hinman - State Files - RNC Delegate Information - Tennessee, 1968 (Box 94, Folder 1289)
    - George Hinman - State Files - RNC Delegate Information - Texas, 1968 (Box 94, Folder 1290)
    - NAR Briefing Sheets - Nevada, Utah, 1968 May 29 (Box 94, Folder 1291)
    - NAR Briefing Sheets - Wyoming, New Mexico, 1968 May 23; 1949-1950 (Box 94, Folder 1292)
    - NAR Briefing Sheets - Colorado, 1968 May 27 (Box 94, Folder 1293)
    - NAR Briefing Sheets - South Carolina, 1968 May 24 (Box 94, Folder 1294)
    - NAR Briefing Sheets - Georgia, 1968 May 24 (Box 94, Folder 1295)
    - NAR Briefing Sheets - West Virginia, 1968 May 23 (Box 94, Folder 1296)
    - NAR Briefing Sheets - Michigan, 1968 May 22 (Box 94, Folder 1297)
    - NAR Briefing Sheets - Maryland, 1968 May 15 (Box 94, Folder 1298)
    - NAR Briefing Sheets - Pennsylvania, 1968 May 15-16 (Box 94, Folder 1299)